{
    "subject": "Saeed_Akhtar_Mirza",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Albert_Pinto_Ko_Gussa_Kyon_Aata_Hai",
    "human_readable": "Saeed Akhtar Mirza directed the film Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9845530986785889,
            "question": "Has Saeed Akhtar Mirza directed any other films besides Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9770609736442566,
            "question": "Who directed the film Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9383072853088379,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by Saeed Akhtar Mirza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9321961998939514,
            "question": "What year was the film Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9055496454238892,
            "question": "Is the film Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai considered a classic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8624293804168701,
            "question": "What genre does the film Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8613998293876648,
            "question": "What is the main theme explored in the film Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8373774886131287,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in the film Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8344285488128662,
            "question": "Is Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai a fictional story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5715920329093933,
            "question": "What kind of work does Saeed Akhtar Mirza do?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Saeed Akhtar Mirza directed the film Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai.",
            "html": "yago_14546_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai a fictional story?",
            "html": "yago_14546_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in the film Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai?",
            "html": "yago_14546_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main theme explored in the film Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai?",
            "html": "yago_14546_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14546_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14546_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14546_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14546_142.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14546_184.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14546_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14546_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14546_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14546_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14546_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents mention Saeed Akhtar Mirza as the director or producer of the film \"Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyon Aata Hai\", which confirms the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Saeed Akhtar Mirza directing the film \"Albert Pinto Ko Gussa Kyoon Aata Hai\" (1980), which supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}